<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Jackson&#x27;s Blog</title>
    <link href="https://verassitnh.github.io/edu/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://verassitnh.github.io/edu" />
    <updated>2021-02-10T15:56:56-06:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Jackson Mooring</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://verassitnh.github.io/edu</id>

    <entry>
        <title>This is a post about politics</title>
        <author>
            <name>Jackson Mooring</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://verassitnh.github.io/edu/this-is-a-post-about-politics/"/>
        <id>https://verassitnh.github.io/edu/this-is-a-post-about-politics/</id>
            <category term="Series: American Politics"/>

        <updated>2021-02-10T15:56:11-06:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p> </p>
<p>sdgsdfgdfgdfdfgdfgdgdfg</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Who I am</title>
        <author>
            <name>Jackson Mooring</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://verassitnh.github.io/edu/who-i-am/"/>
        <id>https://verassitnh.github.io/edu/who-i-am/</id>

        <updated>2021-02-10T15:56:56-06:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://verassitnh.github.io/edu/media/posts/2/ash-edmonds-Koxa-GX_5zs-unsplash.jpg" alt="Colorful Laptop" />
                <h1>Hey Friends 👋</h1>
<p>Hi, my name is Jackson. I am a homeschooled high school student. I am a reader, coder, aspiring entrepreneur, and a child of God. I love to be productive, to be helpful, to give, and to get stuff done. I like to study, work, eat, read, live, and run. My day generally starts at 5AM and ends at 8PM. Every day I spend 2 hours of my time participating in productive recreation. My pleasure reading generally consists of historical fiction or historical non-fiction.</p>
<p> </p>
<h2>Some random facts about me:</h2>
<ul>
<li>I design, code, live, serve, excercise and work.</li>
<li>I look forward to the future.</li>
<li>I am passionate about history.</li>
<li>I am a writer, reader, efficiency enthusiast, homeschooler, and a Christian.</li>
<li>My goal is projection, not perfection.</li>
<li>The wind blows, time flies, and I run.</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p>I like to think that I have a big imagination. I would rather do an extra Algebra lesson than eat a mushroom. I would rather write an extra paper than do an extra Algebra lesson. I love Algebra. I hate mushrooms. My pet-peeve is getting interupted for no reason at all. I have 8 cute siblings.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Skunk War - English 1 Lesson 10 Assignmen</title>
        <author>
            <name>Jackson Mooring</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://verassitnh.github.io/edu/skunk-war-english-1-lesson-10-assignmen/"/>
        <id>https://verassitnh.github.io/edu/skunk-war-english-1-lesson-10-assignmen/</id>

        <updated>2021-02-10T14:06:35-06:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://verassitnh.github.io/edu/media/posts/1/pexels-harrison-haines-3536247.jpg" alt="" />
                <article class="article scrollappear appear appeared"><header class="article-header">
<div class="article-list-footer">
<div class="article-list-tags"><span style="color: var(--text-editor-body-color); font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">It wasn’t that long ago, when on a return trip from locking up the cow, as dusk settled into night, I almost tripped over a skunk. I jumped to the side, but it was already to late. That wicked weasel had left his sticky aroma clinging to my jeans. I smelled bad. Very bad. Right then and there I declared war on skunks.</span></div>
</div>
</header>
<div class="article-content">
<p>It was a bright winter morning, the air was a little chilly, but the sun had come out and warmed the earth. About a week had past since I had declared war on skunks after that wicked creature sprayed me, but that was not on my mind at the moment because I was in the shop feeding the cow. Suddenly, all the chickens around the shop squawked and flew in all directions. Knowing something was wrong, I ran out of the shop. A skunk was running at full speed towards the south fence of our property. I grabbed a heavy metal bar and ran after it. When I felt I was in range, I threw my metal bar at the skunk, and I hit! The skunk stopped running, rolled over two or three times, got back up, and started running again at twice the speed. I threw the bar again and again, but never hit him. The skunk had gotten away once again</p>
<p>Ever since the last skunk incident, I have always carried a gun when I went out to do stuff with the cows. Well, this time it was a dark, cold, foggy, winter night. As I trudged through 70 acres of that tall winter grass, I thought about all sorts of things, that I would never have had time to reflect on, had I not, every morning, and every evening, when it was dark, light, cold, hot, foggy, rainy, stormy, snowy, windy, when the stars were bright, or when they weren’t, trudged through that familiar grass, to lock up that familiar cow. This time I thought about skunks. I though a lot about skunks. I thought about when I would see skunks, and when I would shoot them. But, I finally concluded that as long as I was expecting to see a skunk, I wouldn’t see one. So, as I trudged on, my thoughts wandered on. My muse got deeper and deeper, ‘til I was moving mechanically, to do the chore so deeply ingrained in muscle memory. I trudged on and on. The night got darker and darker. The sun sank beneath the mountains to the far west.</p>
<p>I was suddenly awakened to reality, to see a white streak (the trademark symbol of the striped skunk), dart across the path 30 yards in front of me. Without the slightest hesitation, I pulled my single-action .22 revolver from its holster. I had six shots, numb fingers, and a moonless and foggy night. I started running. The chase had begun.</p>
<p>Every time I pulled the trigger, a blinding flash of light, and a hollow-point capsule of death, shot out that 7” barrel. After three shots, the critter was dead.</p>
<p>And so closes one of the many stories that weaves into the greater story of me. We all have stories, we all have lives, that weave together into the greater story of the one who created us. We are living <em>His</em> story.</p>
</div>
</article>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
